vletuknow.com 2018-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Vletuknow

## Privacy Policy for Vletuknow.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us here](http://vletuknow.com/contact-us/).

At [Vletuknow.com](http://vletuknow.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Vletuknow.com and how it is used.

**Log Files:**

Like many other Web sites, Vletuknow.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**External Links:**

Our Site may provide links to various third party websites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between our site and that destination site, we do not exercise authority over these linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. We do not assume responsibility or liability and are not responsible for the independent policies and procedures of destination sites. Similarly, we cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such websites. However, we wish to ensure the integrity of our site and any destination links, so any comments pertaining to any website accessed through these links are greatly appreciated.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

Vletuknow.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Amazon Associates Program Disclosure:**

Vletuknow.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie:**

.:: Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Vletuknow.com  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Vletuknow.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –[ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include…

  * **Google Adsense**
  * **Commission Junction**
  * **Clickbank**
  * **Amazon Associates**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Vletuknow.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Vletuknow.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Vletuknow.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
